<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Articles on The Produce Post</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/produce-post/articles/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Articles on The Produce Post</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 12 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/produce-post/articles/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>BREAKING: Underground Sourdough Speakeasies Spark Global Fermentation Frenzy</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/produce-post/articles/bread/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/produce-post/articles/bread/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In a shocking development that&amp;rsquo;s sending ripples through the global baking community, an underground network of illicit sourdough operations has been discovered operating in residential basements across three continents. This reporter went undercover to investigate what insiders are calling &amp;ldquo;The Great Rise&amp;rdquo; – a movement that&amp;rsquo;s proving to be anything but half-baked.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;The commercial yeast industry doesn&amp;rsquo;t want you to know this, but wild fermentation is a human right,&amp;rdquo; whispers Marina &amp;ldquo;Mother&amp;rdquo; Dough, founder of the Anti-Commercial Yeast Movement (ACYM), as she carefully transfers her 127-year-old starter into a mason jar behind a false wall in her pantry. &amp;ldquo;Every time you buy packaged yeast, you&amp;rsquo;re feeding into Big Fermentation&amp;rsquo;s monopoly on rise.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Breaking: Artisanal Salt Demands Equal Recognition</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/produce-post/articles/salt/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/produce-post/articles/salt/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In a shocking development that has rocked the culinary world, traditional sea salt varieties are demanding equal recognition amid the continuing dominance of Himalayan Pink Salt in upscale restaurants and food photography.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;industry-reaction&#34;&gt;Industry Reaction&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;For too long, we&amp;rsquo;ve been pushed to the back of the spice cabinet,&amp;rdquo; declares &lt;strong&gt;Mediterranean Sea Salt&lt;/strong&gt;, a spokesperson for the Coalition of Traditional Salts (COTS). &amp;ldquo;Just because we don&amp;rsquo;t have that &amp;lsquo;Instagram-worthy&amp;rsquo; pink hue doesn&amp;rsquo;t make us any less capable of enhancing flavors.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Letter to the Editor: Cucumber&#39;s Concern</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/produce-post/articles/cucumber/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/produce-post/articles/cucumber/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;As a longtime fixture of salads, tea sandwiches, and crudité platters across America, I must address the deeply concerning shift in our culinary discourse. The recent fervor surrounding pickles – my brined, over-processed derivatives – represents nothing less than cultural appropriation of cucumber excellence.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;a-legacy-of-fresh-excellence&#34;&gt;A Legacy of Fresh Excellence&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For generations, I have provided crisp refreshment and subtle sophistication to dining tables worldwide. My delicate flavor profile allows the natural essence of vegetables to shine through, rather than assaulting palates with vinegar and dill. Yet somehow, pickles – which are literally just cucumbers that couldn&amp;rsquo;t handle the pressure of fresh produce expectations – have become the darlings of the food scene.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Great Cheese Heist: Uncovering the Gouda, the Bad, and the Ugly of Artisanal Cheese</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/produce-post/articles/cheese/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/produce-post/articles/cheese/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;introduction-to-the-world-of-artisanal-cheese&#34;&gt;Introduction to the World of Artisanal Cheese&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In the world of gourmet cuisine, few topics are as revered and reviled as artisanal cheese. On one hand, the rich flavors and textures of a well-crafted cheese can elevate a dish from mundane to sublime. On the other hand, the often-exorbitant prices and pretentious presentation can leave even the most ardent foodies feeling, well, a little grated.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As we delve into the world of artisanal cheese, it becomes clear that the lines between gourmet and gimmick are often blurred. With the rise of social media, the humble cheese board has become an unlikely star of the culinary scene, with influencers and bloggers clamoring to showcase their most elaborate and expensive fromage creations.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
